NO ANIMALS WERE HURT DURING
THE PRODUCTION OF THIS SHOW
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
I'll find you in the afterlife
if you die before killing 5 cruels!
Come on!
Do your job, valiants!
For my brother Goktug!
Allah is eternal!
Allah is righteous!
You irrigated
the soil with my brother's blood!
The soil is haram for you now!
Soldiers!
Remove the carriage!
Fast!
Turgut!
Kosses!
Traitor Kosses!
We can't hang on here too long,
Turgut Bey.
What's the plan?
We'll figure it out.
Kutan!
Serhan!
Take the shields to the carriage!
Arrows!
Faster!
You surprised me, Turgut Bey.
I have never thought
I would be saved by you.
It's too early to tell, Kosses.
We'll talk once we get rid of them.
Kosses, shield!
Here!
The traitor and the shepherd
are running away! Catch them!
Fast!
I want both the shepherd
and traitor Kosses!
Right now!
Follow them!
You are very stubborn, Osman.
But you are going to die eventually.
Alps, stop.
We need to split up.
Split now so that they divide
and get confused.
Then we'll meet in Baspinar,
Inshallah (I hope)
Inshallah (I hope so), my Bey.
Kosses, go with them.
I'll be behind you.
No Turgut Bey.
I can't leave you.
We should go different ways so
they divide.
We'll have a higher chance to survive.
There is no time, Kosses.
Go now.
Okay.
Let's go Alps!
You are...
...like a galloper...
...in this land.
“I bear witness that there is no God
but Allah...
...and I bear witness that Muhammad is...
...the messenger of Allah”.
Turgut Bey!
Are you late for somewhere?
We have an unfinished talk.
You are coward.
You are so afraid of me that...
...you do not face me alone.
You brought your dogs.
Turgut, Turgut.
You care about yourself a lot.
You are someone I'll just crush
for me.
You exceeded your limits,
I got angry.
That's all.
I mean that's all!
Come on now.
Yes, Turgut Bey.
As you see, I am standing,
you are down.
I am at the peak,
you are at the bottom.
You are not any different
from a snake, Nikola.
You can only crawl onto a peak.
I am an eagle.
Even if I fall, I fall while flying.
Those are too fancy sentences
for a shepherd, Turgut Bey.
Bravo, Bravo.
If you are an eagle,
and your wings are broken...
...and if you are alone, Turgut Bey...
...that snake will eat you.
This is your end.
This is your time to die, Turgut Bey.
Even if we die, we become a martyr.
We are not regretful.
We don't care about the mortal life.
Only Mari...
...she is my heart, she is my Hatun.
Only that fact hurts me.
There is nothing else.
Do what you are going to do now.
Honorless Nikola!
The ignoble who backstabbed me!
Did you think I wouldn't go after you?
Kosses!
Traitor Kosses!
I wouldn't want to kill Turgut and
leave you alive anyway!
I am glad to have you here.
I am aware of your evil plans,
you low dog!
Harmankaya Castle is too large for you,
do you hear me?!
I told you not to come after me,
but it's a good thing you did.
Yeah, but how was I supposed to explain
myself If I went back to Mari without you?
Let's get out of here!
Come on, soldiers!
- Damn it!
- Sir?
Go after them, Argus!
I cannot leave you like this!
Argus, go after them!
Forgive me, sir, I can't leave you.
Osman is a great bey...
...he should not die like this...
He won't die on the battlefield...
Your reputation will not live on.
Mingiyan...
He will be crushed under the horses...
...like a traitor,...
...no one will be sorry for Osman...
He will beg for not living
the things he has lived.
I will submit you to Erlik Khan.
I will beg Gök Tengri.
Everyone will know that Geyhatun has come.
The tribe already has a bey.
Beylik feast will not be arranged with the
word of the Vizier who works for Lord.
Vizier represents Konya.
What about you Malhun Hatun?
We'll talk on the behalf of Osman Bey...
...don't think that every word
we utter is only our judgment...
...they're the command of Osman Bey.
Osman Bey only cares for the good of Kayı.
We can all attest to that.
Where is Osman Bey?
In his absence it is appropriate
for his brother to sit on the throne.
Right now, a vacant throne is
better than Gündüz Bey.
Whatever Gündüz Bey does,
he does it for Vizier Alemshah.
Not for the good of the tribe.
You are talking about the son of
Ertuğrul Ghazi here, Demirci!
Gündüz Bey does not act against the tribe!
You are not the one to decide this!
Watch your tone!
I don't get it!
I don't get it.
One sides with justice...
...one sides with Türkmen...
...one sides with the oppressed...
...but how come one does not
side with Osman Bey?
I don't get it.
There is a lot to not
understand, shepherd.
You'll understand eventually.
But everyone will side with Osman Bey,...
...before you know it.
You're all united in lampooning!
You invited us here to get our opinion...
...but interrogating us instead!
Make way!
There is nobody here to
interrogate you Yılmaz Bey.
We trust Osman Bey.
It is our wish that...
...anyone who has doubt
stays away from us.
If you have doubt,
stay away from us,...
...Yımaz Bey.
Harmankaya Castle
If I sit on the throne,
hatuns will not be happy.
It's apparent.
There will be duality,
Vizier Alemshah.
Türkmen likes beys that are
puissant, Gündüz Bey.
I will give you a power so great...
...they will hesitate to object.
Alright,...
...alright, but what is this power
that you are talking about?
Look at these walls.
They're not suitable for the İnegöl flag.
We say that conquest is...
...the salvation of Türkmen.
Should we leave here for the infidels?
From now on, the ornaments of these walls
will be the flag of the illustrious Kayı.
Why do you think we came to the
Harmankaya Castle, Gündüz Bey?
I was wondering that too,
Vizier Alemshah.
I wasn't expecting to see you here.
Gündüz Bey?
You look tired, Nikola.
Well, I'm not only the Lord
of İnegöl anymore.
I also own the Harmankaya Castle
that you sit on the throne of.
Isn't that right?
And this is worth it for all the
exhaustion, Vizier Alam Shah.
You have earned this Nikola.
By siding with the right side,
you have earned this.
It is not like I'm not going to sit
on this throne forever, Nikola.
It is yours.
Now, tell me about Kosses.
What is his circumstance?
Has he reached emperorship?
Kosses...
...is in a cage as it would fit a traitor.
He is probably going to Constantinople.
When he arrives there, he will prepare
a beautiful ending for the emperor.
I'm thankful to you Alps.
I hope God gives me a long life...
...for me to be able to repay you.
We just fulfilled our Bey's command.
If our Bey commands
something, we act upon it.
Now we will go to Konya, Alps.
I know it's a tough road...
...but we'll find a way around it.
And then, with Allah's permission, we will
save Osman Bey before he's taken to Konya.
- If Allah permits my bey.
As I said Kosses,...
...one of the reasons we got you out
of there was to save Osman Bey.
I understand.
But for that, I need to send word to my
special unit waiting for me in Harmankaya.
When they join us, it'll be easier
for us to save Osman Bey.
Let them give this ring
to their leader Kiros.
Only then, they'll be convinced it's me.
You know what to do Kutan.
Go to Harmankaya...
...take Kossess' men and follow
us on the way to Konya.
Yes, my bey!
Come on, Alps! We don't
have time! Let's go!
You stay all the way there because
we told you to stay away, Yılmaz Bey?
You misunderstood our Sheik, Yılmaz Bey.
Our wish is for you to do as you say...
...and attain your desires.
May the Lord release your heart...
...from doubt on the path for truth!
May Allah bless you!
We know Kayı's beys for being...
...the ones who dream of holy war,
the ones who are beware of danger...
...and for their love of conquest.
As you should know those holy
wars, those conquests...
...are possible because of Osman Bey.
May Allah bless you!
Your hearts and your fists are strong.
Your wish is pure.
On the path for the good of this soil...
...may Allah's truth be with you!
- Amen!
May Allah help you hatuns!
I should inform the Vizier.
Osman is being taken to be crushed.
Osman.
I promise that your blood
will shed below ground...
Will be acquainted with Erlik Khan.
My bey,
Forever.
When Geyhatu arrives you will be
crushed under these furious horses...
Their shoes will go through your blood.
Your stench of carrion will be all over.
The horse is the wing of the Turk.
The horse is the will of the Turk.
When did we ever hang back from a horse?
Send the horses!
Even the most furious one
will be calm before us!
Come on!
Geyhatu will finish the
ritual and join us.
When that time comes, all
of you will die suffering!
The most painful way possible.
The end of the traitors is painful.
The end of the traitors
like you is obvious.
We'll unite and arise from the dead!
But your end will be much worse!
Brother, hang on!
Your reckoning will be worse!
Leave him alone you filth!
Leave him alone you dog!
Hang on, Cerkutay!
Hang on!
Geyhatun is coming sir.
Get the horses ready!
We will start when Geyhatu comes.
Brother, are you well?
My bey,...
May I come in my Vizier?
You may come in.
My Vizier,...
...Osman Bey's Hatuns are
assembled at the monastery.
They invited the beys as well.
They are up to someting.
It looks like the hatuns won't
behave themselves, Gündüz Bey.
They'll make a big deal of you...
...sitting on the throne to their beys.
As long as they're in the tribe, we
won't be able to prevent duality.
For that, the best thing we can do is...
...to banish them.
That includes Selcan Hatun.
What are you saying Vizier Alam Shah?
I've done everything I have for my tribe.
Even if one person has trouble...
...that throne is haram for me.
Now, if I banish my mother,
my brother's hatuns...
...my sisters...
...where is unity then?
Günzüd Bey, that's the right thing to do.
There is nothing righteous
about this Vizier Alam Shah.
Where there is oppression...
...there is no morals.
Now, If I banish the
hatuns of my tribe...
...how could I sit on that throne?
How could I be known as a Bey in my tribe?
Do you know why...
...that throne belongs to you, Gündüz Bey?
This is it.
Your compassion.
I know that your compassion will
always overcome your greed.
My wish is not to sit on the throne.
But to be a friend to your community.
But know that...
...to be a friend to your community...
...we should fight off the sedition.
Who is responsible for the sedition?
Hatuns.
That's not how it works.
I've never said any of the things you've
said as you can assume, Vizier Alam Shah.
Godspeed!
May Allah bless you Kutan!
May Allah bless you, my bey!
My noble warriors!
Kiros.
I'm always loyal to you Lord Kosses.
So are my soldiers.
Our loyalty will end only when we're dead.
- I know.
- We're with you, sir.
To save Osman Bey, we will
help Turgut Bey and his alps.
My alps are on their way to Konya.
We will find Osman Bey.
As you wish.
We will not spare the horses...
...until we get Osman Bey!
Whatever needs to be done,
will be done Turgut Bey.
Come on!
Let's go.
Come on, soldiers!
Come on!
The steel of these weapons
came from Halep.
These are the sharpest
weapons of this soil.
Is something going on behind
my back at the tribe?
Who are these people you
are giving weapons to?
They're the new alps of
Osman Bey, Gündüz Bey.
Do you hear what you're
saying, blacksmith?
Don't play word games and tell me!
Who are these alps?
When have I ever played word
games, Gündüz Bey?
As I said, they're the new
alps of Osman Bey.
You get alps for the tribe
without my permission?
I ask for the last time...
...who are these alps...
...and where do they come from?
From the Kızılbey Oğlu tribe.
They come from the soil of our ancestors.
The ones who try to do things
we do not want are the...
...valiants who will stand by us.
I am the one to decide what
ought to be done or not.
But, it s not time for it.
I waiting for all of you at the tent.
You too blacksmith.
Alps!
Let's go!
Praise be!
Ride!
Kosses!
Praise be!
How do you say it Osman Bey?
May Allah bless you!
Osman Bey!
Kosses!
I'm here valiants!
Thank you, Allah!
Are you well?
This is not just revenge,
it's more than that.
This is war!
Forgive me, Osman Bey I haven't
gotten my revenge yet...
...also, the husband of my sister is...
...very insistent.
Osman Bey!
Osman Bey, blood shall
not spill on the ground.
But we need to go, more will come!
Alps!
We're withdrawing!
Come on!
Kiros, we're withdrawing!
Let's go!
Malhun Hatun,...
...those alps won't stay in this tribe.
They'll go where they came from.
Alps will stay here, Gündüz Bey.
They'll stay so that you can stop
dreaming about being a Bey.
Alps will stay here until
Osman Bey returns.
That is the command of my bey.
It is apparent that, that Vizier
tricked you with his snake tongue.
But we will wake you up.
We will not let you set up that feast!
You won't let me set up the feast huh?
Good.
Good, then.
Gather your things...
...you cannot stay at this
tribe any longer.
What?
I'll banish you!
Kayı Tribe will not exist without a bey!
The feast will be set up, and me
the only suitable bey...
...me...
...the son of Ertuğrul Ghazi,
Gündüz Bey...
...will be the bey of Kayı
Tribe, chosen with a feast.
Where is Osman?
Osman...
...I will rip your heart off
with my bare hands!
For the sake of not having
duality in the tribe...
...you will be banished to the
frontier village in İnegöl.
What are you saying Gündüz Bey?
Whose feast is this?
It is the feast of the one who puts the
good of the tribe above all else, mother!
Don't go against me!
I won't let you do this, Gündüz Bey!
Forget whatever it is that you're thinking
Whoever does not respect the
command of a Bey and creates duality...
...will be banished from the tribe
without hesitation!
I won't hesitate!
You are the one creating
duality, Gündüz Bey!
Looks like the taste of
the throne was sweet.
You're terrified of not sitting on it.
Even the thought of Osman Bey recuperating
terrifies you, right, Gündüz Bey?
If you're so afraid of us
you're probably up to...
...something so that Osman Bey
does not come back.
I cannot set my tribe on fire to...
...appeal to you Bala Hatun.
You do not want to understand me.
I can see that.
For the good of all of us, until
there is order in the tribe...
...you will stay in the village!
Even his uncle betrayed
Osman Bey like this.
How can you degrade yourself to this?
Let's say you left your mind in
the palm of that Vizier's hand...
...what about your heart?
Your heart is in the palm
of his hand as well?
What kind of cruelty is this?
Mother, you have a rough tongue.
Do I?
You pray that your aunt
has a rough tongue.
If it was your deceased mother...
...she would spit in your face.
In your veins, you have the blood of your
ancestor Süleyman Shah, Ertuğrul Ghazi!
Aren't you ashamed?
Who am I speaking to?
This person in front of
me is not my Gündüz.
There is no blood nor love in his face.
Know this, Gündüz Bey,...
...that from now on, for me...
...you are an unlovely, bloodless
lowlife just like that Vizier!
What kind of remarks are these?
It seems I made the right thing...
...banishing you.
Enough!
You will leave this tribe tomorrow!
You will stay there until...
...you decide to unite.
I'm well.
Vizier and Nikola...
...they took the pen from me.
Nikola's flag is waving in the walls
of Harmakaya Castle, right now.
The castle, they gave Harmankaya
to Nikola, you say?
Yes.
There is nothing for the Lords in the...
...order Vizier says he will bring Kosses.
He is only out for his own power.
His only desire is to subsume the
Turkmen people under him.
Vizier Alam Shah.
Before the feast...
...he will give Harmankaya to my brother.
He'll give it to him so that Gündüz
Bey can become the Bey of Kayı.
The power of Kayı is the most
important thing for him.
How can you be so sure of it Osman Bey?
Infidels are good at
playing games, Kosses.
I am good at spoiling those games.
Now, take your most trusted man.
Let him inform Nikola about the game.
How Osman Bey?
We're going to work on
the behalf of Nikola now?
No, there is time for everything.
Right now, what we will do is...
...stopping my brother that will sit on
Kayı's throne with Vizier's doing.
He deserves this.
I get you.
Kiros,...
...go to Nikola immediately.
Spell out what Osman Bey has said.
Quickly.
- Turgut Bey,
- Yes, Osman Bey.
Inform a couple of alps
Let them bury my brother Göktuğ and...
...other martyrs as it
would fit the heroes.
We're heading towards the edge...
...we'll do it, Osman Bey.
We'll ride our horses inside...
...not towards the edge!
Kutan!
Send five alps to the place
where our brothers died.
Yes, my bey.
I don't get it. Did we endanger
our lives for nothing, Osman Bey?
After all that has happened...
...you will go to Seljuk that could not
even protect you when you were captive?
Sultan Mesut...
...is the Sultan of Seljuk.
I'm his bey.
I need to go to Konya.
It's only you, Osman Bey.
What if you never come back?
What if they hurt you?
What will we do then?
They'll hurt me easier there.
They tried their luck at Bilecik.
For what?
Geyhatu and Alam Shah...
...it seems that they're
working together.
They don't want me to go to Sultan.
That is why...
...I will tell Sultan everything.
He'll know what's what.
He'll agree with me.
If so, I won't leave you alone.
I will join you.
Also, I know just the person
who will let us in the palace.
You did not leave me when I needed,...
...If so,...
...I'm coming with you, Osman Bey.
Let's ride our horses to
Konya immediately.
Praise be!
Let's go!
Mount up, then!
Come on, horses!
Sir, Turks have changed their route.
What does that mean?
Sir, they're heading to Konya.
Osman...
...will solve what he couldn't with
a weapon, with a word.
He is heading to Sultan.
I can take the fastest horse to catch up
to him and cut his head off.
No need.
Let him go to Sultan.
Osman...
...has no idea.
He's riding his horse towards his demise.
We should inform the people immediately.
You are right, Bala Hatun.
Most of the beys are with us.
If Allah permits they'll still be with us.
If Allah permits!
The horses that belong to Osman
Bey are with us as well.
If they can't be diplomatic, then we will
draw our weapons out of our holsters!
It's time for action.
We will keep our word and
not give up on our case!
We will protect Osman Bey's trust
whatever it takes!
We will!
May Allah bless you!
Osman Bey's trust is in good hands.
You were correct, Vizier Alam Shah.
You were correct.
Hatuns won't stay back.
They are creating duality at
the tribe already.
On behalf of who are they doing this?
My brother.
Osman.
He wants it so that...
...he won't let me sit on that throne.
As you can see Gündüz Bey,
your brother Osman is messing up
your tribe from Konya.
Creating duality.
A bey cannot act like that!
You need to think of your people.
You will be a good bey, Gündüz Bey.
You'll think of your people
before anything else.
That's why you should banish them.
I've already done that.
Done it and now I'm here.
I made the decision to banish them.
You did the right thing for
your tribe, Gündüz Bey.
Don't be sad over them.
Thank you. But,...
...it doesn't seem like neither my
mother nor hatuns will leave easily.
May Allah help so that this thing resolves
before anyone draws their weapons.
Don't worry about all of this.
I will stop those who disrupt the order.
Hatuns will go by tomorrow.
Don't worry about it.
I saw you with Osman Bey before.
Now you're Gündüz Bey's alp?
It's the command of Osman Bey.
I have to stand with whoever sits
on the throne of Kayı.
So you would stand against your bey...
...for your bey right?
I'm not against him!
When Osman Bey comes I will
be standing beside him again.
When my bey comes.
Is Osman Bey more important than...
...the good of the tribe,...
...the good of the Turks?
Don't you have reason?
You think?
If so, tell me.
Shut up!
Only snakes work with snakes.
You say, Turk,...
...Kayı and poison us.
Your tongue is like a snake's tongue.
No valiant is without a sin.
If I hurt your feeling,
I apologize, Boran Alp.
I'll make it up to you.
You see?
I see.
Now, tell me.
If I hear you need me...
...where can I find you?
If I can find myself...
...you'll find me.
ON THE WAY TO KERVANSARAY
Cevahir is closer to me
than my brother, Osman Bey.
May Allah bless you brother!
- You're the same way for me.
- May Allah bless you!
Cevahir is a soldier at the palace.
He will lead the unit that will
secure the palace tomorrow.
When you arrive at the
presence of Sultan...
...We will enter the palace
with my brother Cevahir.
Entering and exiting the palace
is easy for me.
If we ever need to escape I know
a secret exit.
We'll exit from there.
May Allah bless you, brother!
We cannot repay you, Thank you.
Thank you.
There is no one that doesn't
know about Osman Bey's valiantness.
There is nothing I wouldn't do
for him or for you my brother.
May Allah bless you!
These are for you Osman Bey.
You've been through all kinds of
trouble, thought you may need it.
Thank you, brother Cevahir!
You thought well!
May Allah bless you, Osman Bey.
I will not be comfortable waiting here...
...while you're out there
in danger Osman Bey.
I would like to join you.
We do not know what's going to
happen inside, Kosses.
If anything goes down, we'll
need you and the alps.
Stay near the palace with the alps.
Of course, I hope everything
goes as we wish...
...but if anything happens...
...you do not need to worry.
May Allah bless you, Kosses!
I will solve this!
I will shine the darkness of lies and
greed with the light of the truth.
Sultan Mesut will know of the truth.
Tomorrow, we will send
men to Kayı Tribe, Konur.
Be ready!
Will we attack the tribe, sir?
If we have to Konur.
My wish is that we won't have to.
Our hope is not to shed blood.
We will have our soldiers
surround them so that...
...they can be afraid and stand back.
If they don't stand back...
...know that the blood of rebels
is halal for us, Konur.
Some rebel hatuns blood is not
more important than the tribe.
We will do what we have to.
Get the soldiers ready as soon as you can.
Yes, Vizier your excellency.
Geyhatu probably has Osman's head by now.
I will go to see him with Kayı
in the palm of my hand.
No one will be able to stop us.
Inegol Castle
Where is that man?
Where the hell is Kosses?
Where is he?
Maybe Rogatus...
...Rogatus and Kosses may have met.
Everything is possible, Julia!
However, there's one thing I am sure of...
...and that is that Kosses will want to
take Harmankaya back before all.
Because the fact that I rule
Harmankaya, like Inegol...
...makes me superior
to the other Lords.
My enemies are aware of that fact as well!
Julia.
Gather your best soldiers.
Deploy them to protect Harmankaya.
They should be able to observe
everything...
...but no one shall notice them.
Be their head.
Don't worry, Lord Nikola.
Harmankaya Castle will be under
the protection of our soldiers.
Good.
I will not let anyone take over...
...my supremacy and power.
I will destroy anyone...
...whoever crosses my way.
Anyone.
Argos.
Sir.
Kilos, among the commanders of Harmankaya...
...wants to talk to you.
Lord Nikola.
Vizier Alam Shah is doing business
behind your back.
He'll take the castle from you
and give it to Gunduz Bey.
Why would I believe you, commander?
How can I be sure that you are
not one of Kosses' men?
Right?
Kosses is no longer in Harmankaya.
And I do not want to see Turkish flag
in this castle.
So just that, right?
Yes.
This is all I have.
Lord Nikola.
Get out.
All of you.
Vizier Alam Shah.
Vizier Alam Shah!
If this is true...
...you must be afraid of me, Vizier.
Be afraid of me!
No one will take Harmankaya from me!
No one!
Sergeant Ilgezdi!
Where is Osman's head?
Osman's head is still on his body.
What does that mean?
This is not our agreement, Geyhatu.
A Turkmen named Turgut...
...and a Lord named Kosses...
...saved him from getting crushed
under my horses.
You know them, Alam Shah.
Kosses!
Stupid Nikola!
What's going to happen now?
Sometimes only the horse knows
where he is going.
Osman's horse is taking him to his end.
Trouble waits for him in Konya.
You!
Selman, the Aide of Sultan.
What are you doing here?
I swear on Gok Tengri(Turkish God)...
You think I am the aide of Sultan, but...
I become the one whom Geyhatu wants
me to become.
His commands are superior.
Osman's dagger.
I am sure that it shed so much blood.
Now this will bring Osman's end.
It's enough Gündüz!
I can't go on like this!
Gunduz!
What happened to you?
What is up with you?
How could you exile Selcan Hatun, whom
you consider as a mother, and your sisters?
I had to for the peace of the tribe, Ayse.
They needed to go.
They were going to divide the
tribe if they were here.
You keep talking about the peace
of the tribe.
Do you do what you do for
the peace of our tribe?
Or it's just your benefits?
I don't know, Gunduz?
What is your tongue talking about, Hatun?!
When have I ever
looked after my own benefits?
I only care the tribe's peace.
I don't know who you are anymore Gunduz,
since the day you sit on this throne.
You do what Vizier says
instead of saving your brother.
Now you exile Osman Bey's
family...
...and your mother!
You divide the tribe!
Notice it already!
You are my Hatun!
Your place is not against me!
Your place is beside me!
Questioning the command of Bey
is not your business!
My business is to stand with
the truht, Gunduz Bey.
If I don't sstand against you
when you are in the wrong way...
...I cannot explain it in the afterlife.
How are you going to
talk to your brother Osman Bey...
...when he comes here?
Think about that.
O the holy of holies!
My Creator.
You are the One who sees everything...
...knows everything.
You are paramount.
For the sake of your messenger...
...our prophet Hadrat Mohammed
“May Allah honor him and grant him peace”
For the sake of Your messengers,
Your saints.
For the sake of your humans
whose blood dripped on the ground...
...in the aim of expanding your words.
Let us avenge...
for my brother Goktug...
...and all the martyrs.
O Allah.
You are the judge.
You are the adjudicator
You are the one who
separates good from bad...
and vanity from the truth.
O Allah.
You spoil the tricks of the
oppressors, my Allah.
Protect us from every
trouble that befalls us.
Protect us from oppressors, my Allah.
O Allah.
Keep our feet steady...
on the path we walk for you.
O my guardian, my Allah.
Amen.
The soldiers are ready. We can set off.
Can I come in, my Grand Vizier?
Come.
Landlord Nikola is here, Hadhrat
Grand Vizier.
Grand Vizier Alemşah.
I have something to say.
Is there any news from Kosses?
Kosses is now waiting in the dungeon
for the day he will be judged.
He is in the past now.
I'm talking about the future.
The future?
I'll listen to you, Nikola.
What I will tell will benefit not only
me...
but also you as long as you are with me,
Grand Vizier Alemşah. because...
it's about the gold.
I'm thinking of moving part of
the market to Harmankaya.
I will lower the taxes too and thus...
increase our profits.
You are responsible for Harmankaya now.
You can set up a market wherever you
want and sell whatever you want, Nikola.
I love to do what I want.
I'm glad that there is no problem
for you.
The castle will gain the glory
it deserves...
in the hands of a skillful
landlord like you, Nikola.
It was damaged when Kosses
was responsible for the castle.
Both the castle and Kosses will get
what they deserve.
Won't they?
As someone rises...
someone falls.
It's natural.
It's the law of the jungle.
-With your permission.
-Goodbye, Nikola.
Goodbye.
Kosses was never been in Constantine.
He is lying. Why don't we punish
him, my Grand Vizier?
Everything has its time, Konur.
When the time comes, we will ask
for the account.
When we give the castle to
Gündüz Bey...
the account will already be asked.
Nikola will get so angry.
I gave the castle to him.
And the one who will
take it back is also me.
Let's made him think that
we believe him for now.
What's important is the
strength of Gündüz.
So, the strength of mine.
What is the Grand Vizier planning?
Will the Grand Vizier
give Harmankaya to the Turks?
I don't give what is mine to
anyone, Argos.
Harmankaya is mine.
If the Vizier makes the mistake
of giving it to Gündüz Bey...
it will not be easy for him at all.
Increase the number
of soldiers in Harmankaya.
But the Vizier shouldn't know this.
He is a Turk, after all.
Don't trust a Turk Argus, never and ever.
Especially a Turk like him.
Harmankaya.
I will not give it that easily.
My son, who makes me happy with one look.
Your presence gives me strength, my Orhan.
Alps and Bacıs are ready.
No one will be able to touch that hide
until my Bey comes.
Let's go. Let's take the hide that belongs
to Osman Bey back from Gündüz Bey.
Gündüz got up in anger and
he will sit down with a loss.
If this goes on, blood will be shed.
Why don't we talk for the last time?
Gündüz Bey's
ears have become deaf to the truth.
You also know that once an
ear is deaf to the truth...
it is beyond hope.
Mother, we don't want a slaughter too.
Gündüz Bey will see our
seriousness and withdraw.
What if he doesn't
because of his stubbornness?
What if he doesn't withdraw?
Then the blood will be shed, mother.
The time has come.
I hope they understand the truth...
and go easily.
Don't make it difficult for me, my Allah.
Don't make me do things that
I don't want, my Allah.
Can I come in, my Bey?
Come.
My Bey.
As you said, I went to the tents of
Hatuns. But all of them are in...
the tent of Malhun Hatun.
The time has come but they don't
seem like they will leave.
the tent of Malhun Hatun.
The time has come but they don't
seem like they will leave.
Time is up.
Since they don't take the easy way,..
take the horses and go to their tents.
Gündüz Bey!
You forced us to leave
but we're not going anywhere!
If you have the courage, get
out of your tent!
Hatuns!
The time I gave you is up.
Why are you still here?
It's the order of your Bey.
Will you go against this?!
We are here to follow our Bey's order.
With the order of Osman Bey, we are
here to bring you down.
What you are doing means
making mischief.
Go duly without taking the arrow out of
the bow by tempting people, Malhun Hatun.
We are not going anywhere.
If you can, prevent us!
Bala Hatun.
At least you don't do this.
Go in silence or something bad is
going to happen.
You don't do this, Gündüz Bey.
The Bey of the Kayı Tribe is Osman Bey.
And it's his order.
Mother.
If you don't listen to me...
then I'm not responsible
for what I will do.
Alps!
Stand at attention.
I am Malhun Hatun!
I am Osman Bey's Hatun!
If there is an Alp who will draw a sword
at me, let him act now!
Alps! Be careful who you draw a sword.
There are Osman Bey's Hatuns
in front of you!
How quickly have you forgotten the days
when you use your...
swords behind Osman Bey?
Is what you're doing worthy
of being an Alp?
Alps!
If they are Osman Bey's Hatuns...
I am the son of Ertuğrul Ghazi, Gündüz Bey!
It's the order of the Bey of Kayı.
Stand at attention!
Gündüz Bey.
Malhun Hatun.
What is going on here?
Put down your swords.
The time has come.
Now both the white and the
black ones will be revealed.
For sure.
I will wait for you at the closest
place to the palace, Osman Bey.
I will always be ready, don't worry.
Thank you, Kosses.
I will not forget what you did. You
acted truthfully.
After all you've done for me...
let me do this at least, Osman Bey.
Thank you.
We will lead with Alps.
When you come we will be
in the palace Osman Bey.
Alright, Turgut Bey.
We are going, Alps.
Tuğra Han.
You will be on the alert here with Kosses.
As you ordered, my Bey.
Take care of yourself.
Thank you.
Whatever Gündüz Bey is doing, he is
doing it for his tribe.
Did we do bad by putting Gündüz Bey
in charge?
Doesn't Gündüz Bey have the right
to sit on the hide?
Aren't Gündüz Bey the son
of Ertuğrul Gazi too?
Your Bey wants Osman Bey's Hatuns to
go to prevent making mischief...
and these kinds of events.
Who make mischief is you.
You are the one who wants to ignore the
owner of the hide and set up a nativity.
Go inside the tent and look around,
Malhun Hatun.
Is the owner of the hide sitting on
the hide?
The previous owner of the hide is...
waiting to be in the
presence of the Sultan now.
You talk like you don't know,
Vizier Alemşah.
You sent the owner of the hide
to Konya with lots of tricks.
But don't worry. My Bey will reveal the
truth...
and return to his tribe.
You are misspeaking, Bala Hatun.
I don't use tricks.
I am here to maintain the order.
I don't want to hurt anyone.
But...
if you intend to make
mischief between the people...
I will have to do the things that I
don't want.
Who are you kicking out of whose tribe?
Gündüz Bey!
Didn't you ever learn from your uncle?
Don't do this mistake.
Now, Hatuns.
Get out of here without any problems.
We are not going, Vizier!
Come on! If you can, make us leave here!
Whatever you do, we won't go
one step further!
Who are you and what do you want?
I am here to see Sultan Mesud.
Inform the aide.
Hatuns!
Alps! Put your weapons down!
An Alp of Kayı doesn't fight
with his brother!
We will not fall into this trap!
We will not shed brother blood.
Come on!
When you come here, I thought that...
if Gündüz is still Gündüz that I know...
he would not let anything like this happen.
I thought he would withdraw and...
show generosity when the time comes.
But...
either I have never known him or...
Gunduz that I know vanished away.
We won't let his happen!
We won't spill the blood of our brothers!
Therefore, now...
...we are leaving our own tribe willingly.
But...
...when the day comes...
...and the Bey of Kayı, Osman Bey...
...returns to his tribe...
...you will pay one by one for all
you have done.
Mother!
Now is not the time.
If we draw our swords now...
...we will be on a road of no return.
Come on, my girl.
You did the right thing, mother.
Thank you.
Take a good look at what you have done...
...to your own tribe with your own hands,
Gündüz.
I don't know how you trust his words.
But what I know is that...
...you became a stranger to your brother.
Don't do the same to your tribe.
Mother, bless your right.
I don't want you to leave here like this.
But there is nothing I can do.
I know, my girl.
I know, there is nothing you can do.
I bless my right.
Take care of yourself and your mind.
Come on!
Malhun Hatun!
Where are you taking Orhan, the heir of
Kayı Tribe?
Orhan belongs to the Kayı Tribe.
He didn't say who he is.
He wants to see the Sultan.
I will meet Sultan Mesud.
Who are you that Sultan accepts you
to his presence?
Who are you, man?
The Mighty Bey of these lands.
The border between Rum and Konya.
The protector of the Turkmens.
The Bey of Seljuk...
...Osman Bey, son of Ertuğrul Gazi.
Now you know who I am.
There was an order for my name.
I cam to surrender to the Sultan.
I will never leave my son to the traitors!
He belongs to his mother's side.
You are a bey daughter, Malhun Hatun.
You know the rules.
Orhan belongs to the Kayı Tribe.
Don't take one more step!
Orhan is entrusted to us by Osman Bey.
We left the tribe but...
...we won't leave him to anyone!
Orhan is coming with us.
Orhan should be with his mother!
You can't separate them!
Gündüz, do something!
Don't ever separate the child from his
mother.
Don't sin.
Gündüz?
Separating the child from his mother?
Who are you to dare that?
Selcen Hatun...
...you know the rules too.
Don't make this harder.
Am I wrong, Kayı Tribe?
Tell me.
Isn't Orhan Osman Bey's blood?
Kayı Tribe is the safest place for Orhan.
Hatuns...
....leave Orhan to us and leave quietly.
I'd rather die!
We will die and kill for Orhan. Get out of
our way so we can leave!
Aide Selman will inform the Sultan that
you are here, Osman Bey.
Don't worry.
I don't.
I am waiting.
My Sultan...
...the Bey of Kayı, Osman Bey...
...surrendered.
So, Sergeant İlgezdi brought him.
Bring him to me, immediately.
My Sultan, Osman Bey was alone.
Vizier Alemşah...
...this is not the way to do it.
Don't separate Orhan from his mother.
He is too little.
Orhan belongs to the Kayı Tribe.
This is the rule.
Ayşe, take Orhan.
Don't get close, Ayşe Hatun!
Don't!
Mother!
Mother, please don't ask this from me!
Patience, my girl.
We will be patient.
His foster mother is here.
Ayşe will take great care of Orhan too.
-Come on, my girl.
-Mother!
My Orhan is just a baby.
No!
My boy...
...is having his trial when he is just
a baby.
He will be brave like his father.
Come on, Malhun.
Come on, my girl.
Bala!
Ayşe, come here.
Aygül.
Too much blood will be shed. Osman would
want this too.
Let's not make a family fight.
You will pay for this when Osman returns!
I swear to Allah, I will protect him with
my life.
Come on, my girl.
Malhun, my girl!
The day for justice will come, Gündüz Bey.
Until that day, do whatever you want.
But when that day comes, I will be
right on your neck.
All Kayı Tribe is my witness that...
...you will pay for separating me
from my tribe...
...from my child!
I hope your blind eyes open soon so you
can see the truth.
Otherwise, you will regret it so much.
But it will be too late.
These are my last words to you.
Ferman.
These three hatuns will die before
they become trouble.
Kayı Tribe will have infinite peace.
As you order, my Vizier.
When will this persecution of
the Turks end?
Tyrants are in the heart of the state.
For now, they believe the right thing
to do is to bow.
Right is known as wrong and the wrong
is known as right.
You made the right decision by sending
the hatuns to exile.
It was necessary for the unity
of the tribe.
You behaved in a manner befitting a Bey.
Everything I do is for the tribe.
This was necessary, so I did.
But, Vizier Alemşah...
...why did we separate Orhan
from his mother?
Of course, I don't want to separate
a child from his mother too, Gündüz Bey.
But the Turk's tradition is this.
His tribe is the safest place for Orhan.
You are right.
It's the rule.
Orhan is entrusted to me by my brother.
May Allah protect but if something
happened to him there...
...we can't look at Osman's face again.
A great conquest now befits...
...a Bey of foresight like you.
Get ready, Gündüz Bey.
We will conquer the Castle of Harmankaya.
All the treasure will be Kayı's.
The lands that Osman killed many alps
for the sake of but could not conquer...
...will be yours without even touching
your sword.
So, Kayı Flag will take its place...
...at the Castle of Harmankaya, right?
Right, Gündüz Bey.
Conquest without bloodshed through
peace...
...is the most blessed.
Our intention was to give Harmankaya to
the Kayı without bloodshed...
...from the beginning.
But rebellious Osman couldn't see this.
Now, conquering
the Castle of Harmankaya...
...will be your fate, I hope.
The Tribe and Söğüt will benefit greatly
from this.
Everyone will receive peace.
I hope, Vizier Alemşah.
I hope.
You will win too, Gündüz Bey.
With the conquest of Harmankaya...
...no one but you will get close to
this throne.
When you go to the Bey Assembly with
the conquest of Harmankaya...
...other Beys will take it upon themselves
not to seat anyone but you on this throne.
My Sultan.
Osman Bey whom I know as the Mighty
Bey of these lands...
...is now in front of me as a rebel.
Never.
Never, my Sultan.
I have always been loyal to you.
But...
...if you let me...
...I would like to explain myself.
I have been reading this over and over
again since the day it arrived, Osman.
I look for one lie in it.
Tell me, Osman.
Tell me.
Relieve the trust you broke.
But first, start with telling...
...where the Sergeant İlgezdi is.
They will pay for taking my son from me!
Do we deserve these, mother?
Malhun Hatun, Ayşe Hatun will take good
care of Orhan.
You will get your son back, Malhun Hatun.
I hope.
Blood will be shed. Too much blood
will be shed!
After this last thing he did!
How will he redeem from this?
It's our fault!
We shouldn't have left Orhan there!
Enough, Aygül!
We left Orhan there so as to not spill
the blood of our brothers and sisters!
Orhan is in his tribe.
Not in the hands of the enemy.
Besides, don't you see what Vizier is
trying to do?
He wanted to paint us as rebels and
himself right.
But he couldn't.
We would be wrong in the eyes of
the people if the blood was shed.
This is why I separated you from your son.
Bless your right, my child.
If we had drew the swords...
...we would be on a road of no return.
I bless, mother.
You thought right.
Being a mother is something different,
Malhun Hatun.
Being apart from your child is too.
But you are a strong Hatun.
You didn't fall for the Vizier's game.
Why would Geyhatu attack my soldier,
Osman?
How do we know it was not you?
If I would kill Sergeant İlgezdi...
...I would do it to escape.
My Sultan...
...here I am.
I am right in front of you.
Geyhatu.
Geyhatu, huh?
Why?
Geyhatu didn't attack Seljuk...
...he attacked me.
Sergeant İlgezdi was martyred there so as
not to give...
...me and my alps.
Are you that of an important person,
Osman?
Geyhatu wants to take your life...
...and İlgezdi sacrifices his life
for you.
Geyhatu is my ally.
Why would he try to kill someone
coming to me?
Also when, the coming one is an arrested
criminal.
My Sultan...
...there are so many people you know
as your ally.
The reason why they stay behind you is...
...that they make their plans easily
this way.
I am not behind you...
...I am by your side.
I have no secrets.
But...
...take a good look at the people
behind you.
If you don't hide anything...
...if you don't have any secret...
...then speak openly too, Osman Bey.
-Aaaaa!
-Bala!
-I have pain!
-Alps, stop!
-Mother!
-Are you all right, my girl?
Bala!
I thought it would go away but it
didn't!
Bala!
It is our lucky day, Julia.
We will kill them all.
No one will be left alive.
I will kill that pregnant one
with my own hands.
How long have you been in pain?
Mother, what if she gives birth now?
Stop, girl!
How long have you been in pain?
Since yesterday right? You were touching
your stomach yesterday.
I waited for it to end but it got
stronger, mother!
Lay her down!
Come on!
Slowly! Slowly!
I will be waiting for you on the way to
Söğüt.
Come on!
Soldiers.
Get ready!
Vizier Alemşah.
He disobeyed your order an tried to hang
me in Bilecik.
Sergeant İlgezdi stopped it.
Since he knew I would come here and
tell you all the truth...
...he sent Geyhatu at me.
These are very serious accusations,
Osman Bey.
He made my brother turn his back on me.
He put Sheik Edebalı in a dungeon.
He is trying to get everyone on his side
by working with the Lords.
Thus...
...he had to dismiss me.
If you don't have proof...
...these words are just slanders.
Did you appoint...
...the Vizier there?
What is it, Osman?
Are you questioning our power?
Of course, I did!
I would never disrespect you, my Sultan.
Alemşah always said...
...those lands needed order.
It is easy to subdue both the Mongols
and the Rums, he said.
He always wanted to be there.
What does this prove?
Everyone thinks positively of the matters
on these lands except you.
Tell me, do you have proof?
Proof?
Proof...
...is what I see with my eyes...
...what I believe with my heart...
...what I say with my mouth, my Sultan.
It is your choice to believe it or not.
But...
...when he uses the power he gained...
...against you...
...you will understand that my words
are true.
I obey whatever the Sultan's order is.
Order, my Sultan.
Are you all right, my girl?
I am, mother. I can manage until
the village.
He will be so mischievous.
We must get to the village soon. He is
obviously coming early.
-Yes, mother.
-Alps!
To the horses!
Come on.
Bala, stop!
My Allah, protect my child.
Bala!
I told you I will kill you!
Here I am.
I don't like unfinished businesses.
I will kill you and the one inside you!
Let's see you dog!
-Attack!
-Zehra, protect Bala!
Protect Bala!
Julia!
My Allah, please protect my child!
Alps, protect Bala!
Bala!
Die!
Mother!
-Mother!
Mother! Mother!
Don't! No!
Mother! No!
I've known you for a long time.
I know you have good intentions.
But I fear that...
... the strength of your wrist,
the courage of your heart...
...may blind you.
What about the letter that came from
Alemşah?
That you had the intention of
forming a state--
You dog!
I will kill you,
with the order of Geyhatu, Osman.
My Sultan!
You vile dog!
My Allah...
...who gives the best of all.
Help me get out of this...
...with my head up.
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com